♪ It's the eye of the tiger ♪
♪ It's the ear of the bat ♪
♪ It's the whiskers
of the catfish ♪
♪ And the walrus... ♪
(Howard:)Hang on. Not that your song
isn't terrible-- it is...
(Howard:)...but how do you mention bats
and leave out sonar?
(Sheldon:)You didn't let me finish.
♪ And also regarding the bat ♪
♪ It has sonar. ♪
KOOTHRAPPALI:
Hey.
(Sheldon:)Hello.
(Raj:)Look,
(Raj:)I know you guys are upset,
but we've talked about it,
(Raj:)and we think it'd be beneficial
(Raj:)for you to be part
of the project.
(Howard:)Well, well, well,
did you hear that, Sheldon?
(Sheldon:)I'm sorry. I was trying
to think of what rhymes
with "nose of the aardvark."
LEONARD:
We want you
(Leonard:)back on the project with us.
(Howard:)Well, well, well, did
you hear that, Howard?